Preliminary Inventory to the Berton W. Crandall Photographs, 1888-1953
Hoover Institution Archives
- PART 1
  - Miscellaneous
    - Russian scroll and two scroll boxes, together with translation of scroll. Gift to Herbert Hoover from the Russian Government for food relief operations in Russia (2 negatives) (Item 100.)
    - Survey map by the Stanford University Survey Team, with photograph of Herbert Hoover and others. Map signed by Herbert Hoover (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 101.)
    - Stanford University - Letter by Herbert Hoover as class treasurer (1 negative and 1 print - see Faculty-Staff News folder in Box 1) (Item 102.)
    - Herbert Hoover and others at United States Food Administration staff luncheon, 1918 July 3, autographed by all attendees (3 negatives and 1 print) (Item 103.)
    - Sons of Gwalia Mine at Mount Leonora, West Australia, set up by Herbert Hoover in 1898 (2 prints), and Chin Chang Mine in China (1 print). Negatives available, including of other photographs taken in Australia and/or China (Item 104.)
    - Herbert Hoover's grandfather (1 negative) (Item 105.)
    - Herbert Hoover's grandmother (1 negative) (Item 106.)
    - Three miscellaneous prints: photographers with their cameras in front of the Hoovers' Stanford home; Senator Hiram Johnson and Senator Tillotson?; and unidentified old woman (3 negatives and 3 prints) (Item 107.)
- PART 2
  Photographs depicting the Stanford campus before the 1906 earthquake and damage resulting from the earthquake, as well as other general photographs:
  - S-1 to S-249
    - Air view, ca. 1918 (negative) (Item S-1.)
    - Air view, ca. 1918 and later (negative and misc. prints) (Item S-2.)
    - Air view of Hoover Home, ca. 1922 (negative and print) (Item S-3.)
    - Air view of Palm Drive, ca. 1922 (negative and print) (Item S-4.)
    - Air map of Stanford before Memorial Hall was built (negative) (Item S-5.)
    - Front of Physics Corner (negative and print) (Item S-6.)
    - Front of Administration Building, 1920 (negative and print) (Item S-7.)
    - Front of Administration Building, 1920 (negative) (Item S-8.)
    - History Building from Art Gallery, 1920 (negative) (Item S-9.)
    - Looking across Lagunita from Lathrop Hill (negative and 2 different prints) (Item S-10.)
    - Looking across Lagunita from Lathrop Hill, ca. 1896 (2 prints) (Item S-10-1.)
    - Stanford across Lagunita, before 1906 (negative and miscellaneous prints) (Item S-11.)
    - Stanford across Lagunita, before 1906 (glass plate and print) (Item S-12(75).)
    - Prints only (Item S-12(74).)
    - Stanford across Lagunita, before 1906, taken from Lookout from Lathrop Place (glass plate) (Item S-13.)
    - Stanford across Lagunita, before 1906 (glass plate) (Item S-14.)
    - Stanford across Lagunita, before 1906 (glass plate) (Item S-15.)
    - Memorial Court and Arch, before 1906 (glass plate) (Item S-16.)
    - Poster of Memorial Arch and Volcano Background (glass plate) (Item S-17.)
    - Memorial Court and Arch, before 1906 (glass plate and print) (Item S-18.)
    - Memorial Arch and "Faith" Statue, before 1906 (glass plate) (Item S-19.)
    - Chemistry Building and Museum from Memorial Arch, 1906 (glass print) (Item S-20.)
    - Physics Building oak tree, 1908 (glass plate) (Item S-21.)
    - Quad from Library before Education Building was built (negative and print) (Item S-23.)
    - Main Library - Miscellaneous views (negative and print) (Item S-24.)
    - Main Library - Miscellaneous views (2 negatives and prints) (Item S-25.)
    - Main Library - Miscellaneous views (negative) (Item S-26.)
    - Main Library - Interior view (1 negative and print) (Item S-27.)
    - Main Library - Exterior views (2 negatives and print) (Item S-28.)
    - Main Library - Two views (negative and print) (Item S-29.)
    - Main Library - Exterior view (negative) (Item S-30.)
    - Main Library - Two views (negative and print) (Item S-31.)
    - Main Library - Exterior view (negative) (Item S-32.)
    - Main Library - Interior view (negative) (Item S-33.)
    - Main Library - Two interior views (negative) (Item S-34.)
    - Main Library - Interior view (negative) (Item S-35.)
    - Main Library - Reports: 1936, 1937 and 1941 (negatives) (Item S-36.)
    - Main Library - Miscellany; signature of William Shakespeare (print and negatives) (Item S-37.)
    - Hoover Library - Stacks and material in library (negatives and prints) (Item S-38.)
    - Statue of Stanford family while located in Memorial Court (glass plate) (Item S-39.)
    - Entrance Gate to Palm Drive - Miscellaneous views (glass plate and print) (Item S-40.)
    - Entrance Gate to Palm Drive (negative and print) (Item S-41.)
    - Entrance gate to Palm Drive (glass plate and print) (Item S-42.)
    - Entrance Gate to Palm Drive (glass plate) (Item S-43.)
    - Entrance Gate to Palm Drive, before 1906 (glass plate and miscellaneous prints) (Item S-44.)
    - Entrance Gate to Palm Drive - Earthquake (print and negative) (Item S-44-1.)
    - Entrance Gate to Palm Drive from flagpole in Palo Alto, 1931, by photographer Ray E. Clark (negative and print) (Item S-45.)
    - Entrance Gate to Palm Drive - Miscellaneous views, including reconstruction of gateway, 1931 February 19 (negative and print) (Item S-46.)
    - Entrance Gate to Palm Drive - Miscellaneous views (negative and print) (Item S-47.)
    - Palm Drive - Miscellaneous views (negative and print) (Item S-48.)
    - Palm Drive - Miscellaneous views (negative and print) (Item S-49.)
    - Basketball Pavilion (negative) (Item S-50.)
    - Basketball Pavilion (negative and print) (Item S-51.)
    - Stanford Bookstore, 1936 October (negative) (Item S-52.)
    - President's Home (later the Music Department) (negative and print) (Item S-53.)
    - President's Home (later the Music Department) (negative and print) (Item S-54.)
    - Toyon and Branner Halls from Alvarado Row, 1920 (negative) (Item S-55.)
    - Museum lobby (glass plate and print) (Item S-56.)
    - Museum front and Quad (glass plate and print) (Item S-57.)
    - Museum and Chemistry Building, 1905 (glass plate and print) (Item S-58.)
    - Museum front, 1905 (negative and print) (Item S-59.)
    - Museum front, 1905 (glass plate and miscellaneous prints) (Item S-60.)
    - Museum front (print) (Item S-60-1.)
    - Museum Chinese bed (glass plate and print) (Item S-61.)
    - Museum painting "Saturday Night at the Mines" by Nahl (negative and print) (Item S-62.)
    - Museum painting "Yosemite Valley" by Thomas Hill (negative) (Item S-63.)
    - Museum painting "Founding of Monterey Mission" (negative) (Item S-64.)
    - Stadium excavation, 1921 June 10 through 1921 September 22 (glass plate, negative and print) (Item S-65.)
    - Stadium excavation (negative) (Item S-65-1 through 5.)
    - Stadium - Bowl (negative and print) (Item S-66.)
    - Stadium - Bowl (negative and print) (Item S-67.)
    - Stadium - Bowl (negative and print) (Item S-68.)
    - Stadium - View of outside the stadium and view of celebration in bowl (negatives) (Item S-69.)
    - Air view of stadium (negative) (Item S-70.)
    - Air view of stadium (negative and miscellaneous prints) (Item S-71.)
    - Air view of stadium (negative and print) (Item S-72.)
    - Air view of stadium (negative and prints) (Item S-73.)
    - Air view of stadium (negative) (Item S-74.)
    - Men's gym, nearly completed, 1906 (glass plate and print) (Item S-75.)
    - Men's gym, destroyed by earthquake, 1906 (glass plate and print) (Item S-75-1.)
    - Men's gym, nearly completed, 1906 (glass plate and print) (Item S-76.)
    - Encina Hall (negative and print) (Item S-77.)
    - Encina Hall - Miscellaneous views (negative and similar print) (Item S-78.)
    - Encina Hall (negative) (Item S-79.)
    - Encina Hall - Dining Room (negative and print) (Item S-80.)
    - Encina Hall - Kitchen (negative) (Item S-81.)
    - Encina Hall (negative) (Item S-82.)
    - Encina Hall (negative) (Item S-83.)
    - Encina Hall (negative) (Item S-84.)
    - Toyon Hall (negative and print) (Item S-85.)
    - Toyon Hall (negative) (Item S-86.)
    - Toyon Hall - Miscellaneous views (negative) (Item S-87.)
    - Toyon Hall - Exterior view (negative) (Item S-88.)
    - Toyon Hall - Exterior view (negative and print) (Item S-89.)
    - Toyon Hall - Exterior view (negative) (Item S-90.)
    - Toyon Hall - Exterior view (negative) (Item S-91.)
    - Toyon Hall - Arches (negative) (Item S-92.)
    - Toyon Hall - Interior view (negative and print) (Item S-93.)
    - Toyon Hall - Stairway (negative and print) (Item S-94.)
    - Toyon Hall - Student's room (negative) (Item S-95.)
    - Toyon Hall - Interior view (negative) (Item S-96.)
    - Toyon Hall - Interior view (negative and print) (Item S-97.)
    - Toyon Hall - Interior view (negative and print) (Item S-98.)
    - Toyon Hall - Interior view (negative and print) (Item S-98-a.)
    - Toyon Hall - Interior view (negative and print) (Item S-99.)
    - Toyon Hall - Interior view (negative and print) (Item S-99-1.)
    - Dormitories (negative) (Item S-100.)
    - Dormitories (negative) (Item S-101.)
    - Dormitories (picture) (Item S-101-1.)
    - Jordan Hall (negative and print) (Item S-102.)
    - Gym - Men's (negative and different print) (Item S-103.)
    - Gym - Women's, miscellaneous views (negatives and prints) (Item S-104.)
    - Roble Hall (old) - Later Sequoia Hall (glass plate) (Item S-105.)
    - Lagunita Court - Front and miscellaneous exterior and interior views (negatives and prints) (Item S-106.)
    - Roble Hall - Miscellaneous views (negatives and prints) (Item S-107.)
    - Stanford Union - Two views (negatives and pictures) (Item S-108.)
    - Stanford Union (negative) (Item S-109.)
    - Stanford Union - Exterior (negative and print) (Item S-110.)
    - Stanford Union - Exterior (negative and print) (Item S-111.)
    - Stanford Union - Through Arches (negative and print) (Item S-112.)
    - Stanford Union - Dining Room (negative and print) (Item S-113.)
    - Stanford Union - Two views (negatives) (Item S-114.)
    - Statue "Angel of Grief" marble Canopy, before 1906 (glass plate and print) (Item S-115.)
    - Statue "Angel of Grief" (glass plate and print) (Item S-116.)
    - Statue "Angel of Grief" (glass plate and print) (Item S-117.)
    - Statue "Angel of Grief" marble Canopy, before 1906 (Item S-118.)
    - Copy photo of seven Stanford etchings by Louis Orr (negatives) (Item S-119.)
    - Fraternity Houses - Miscellaneous views - Chi Psi Lodge (negatives and prints) (Item S-120.)
    - Fraternity Houses - Miscellaneous views (negatives) (Item S-121.)
    - Fraternity Houses - Miscellaneous views - D.U. House with interior and exterior views and group delegates (negatives and prints) (Item S-123.)
    - Fraternity Houses - Miscellaneous views - Kappa Alpha House (negatives) (Item S-125.)
    - Fraternity Houses - Miscellaneous views, interior and exterior - Phi Kappa Sigma (negatives and print) (Item S-128.)
    - Fraternity House - Miscellaneous views - Sigma Chi House - March 1940 (negatives) (Item S-128-1.)
    - Fraternity Houses - Beta Theta Pi, March 1940 (negatives) (Item S-128-2.)
    - Sorority House - Miscellaneous views - Chi Omega (negatives) (Item S-129.)
    - Fraternity Houses - Miscellaneous views - Zeta Psi House (negatives and prints) (Item S-131.)
    - "Angel of Grief" (negative) (Item S-132.)
    - Mausoleum about 1925 - Miscellaneous views (negatives and prints) (Item S-133.)
    - Mausoleum about 1925 (negative and print) (Item S-133-1.)
    - Mausoleum about 1925 (print) (Item S-133-2.)
    - Mausoleum about 1925 (glass plate and print) (Item S-134.)
    - Herbert Hoover and Geology Men, 1895 (glass plate and print) (Item S-135.)
    - Track Team, 1910 (negative) (Item S-136.)
    - Football Team with Herbert Hoover, 1894 (miscellaneous negatives and prints) (Item S-137.)
    - Faculty Baseball Players, 1902 - Faculty-Senior Game (negative) (Item S-138.)
    - Senior Class Roll, 1931 (negative) (Item S-139.)
    - Stanford Faculty, 1896 February 4 (glass plate, negative and print) (Item S-140.)
    - Stanford Faculty, 1891-1892 (negative and print) (Item S-140-2.)
    - Early Photos - Miscellaneous views - Roble, 1896? (picture) (Item S-141.)
    - Early Photos (negative and print) (Item S-141-1.)
    - Early Photos - Dedication, 1891 October (negative and print) (Item S-141-2.)
    - Rowing Team, 1909 (negative) (Item S-141-6.)
    - Early Photos - Engine, Government Stanford C.P.R.R. (negative and print) (Item S-141-8.)
    - Early Photos - Laying the Last Rail - Promontory Point, Joining East-West (negative and print) (Item S-141-9.)
    - Early Photos - Letter dictated by Leland Stanford, 1885 November (negative and print) (Item S-141-10.)
    - Early Photos - Seniors dress for Faculty Baseball Game, 1902 (negative and print) (Item S-141-11.)
    - Early Photos - Alumni Council, 1910 or 1912 (glass plate and print) (Item S-141-12.)
    - Early Photos - University of Berkeley Senior Fence Stealing, 1899, arrival in Quad (negative and print) (Item S-141-13.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - View of Stock Farm from hill (negative and print) (Item S-142-1.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - Horse on track (negative) (Item S-142-2.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - Horses and men in front of Barn (negative) (Item S-142-3.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - Muybridge (negative and print) (Item S-142-4.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - Experiment in Motion (negative) (Item S-142-5.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - Horses with Sulkies (negative) (Item S-142-6.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - Horses and carriages in front of Barn (negative) (Item S-142-7.)
    - Stock farm Photos - Stables - Horse (Electioneer) (negative) (Item S-142-8.)
    - Stock farm Photos - Horse Statue (negative) (Item S-142-9.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - Stock farm Horse Statue (negative and print) (Item S-142-10.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - In Commemoration. The Motion Picture Research conducted in 1879 at Palo Alto Farm, now Stanford (negative and print) (Item S-142-11.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - Monument listing famous trotting horses (negative and print) (Item S-142-12.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - Action Photos. First Movies (negative and print) (Item S-142-13.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - Action Photos. First Movies (negative) (Item S-142-14.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - Experiment in Motion: Horse Made by Muybridge (negative and print) (Item S-142-15.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - Experiment in Motion: Dog Made by Muybridge (negative) (Item S-142-16.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - Experiment in Motion: Deer Made by Muybridge (negative) (Item S-142-17.)
    - Stock Farm Photos - Experiment in Motion: Man Made by Muybridge (negative) (Item S-142-18.)
    - First Men's Gym (negative and print) (Item S-143.)
    - Front of Old Quad, 1898 (2 negatives and 1 print) (Item S-144.)
    - Memorial Hall - Miscellaneous views (negatives and print) (Item S-145.)
    - Memorial Hall (print) (Item S-145-1.)
    - Front Façade across Oval Lawn with "Faith" Statue (negative) (Item S-147-1.)
    - Front Façade (negative and print) (Item S-147-2.)
    - Front Façade before 1906 (negative and print) (Item S-147-3.)
    - Front Façade (glass plate and print) (Item S-148.)
    - Front Façade (negative) (Item S-148-1.)
    - Front Façade from Physics Corner, 1910 (glass plate) (Item S-149.)
    - Front Façade from Frame of Library, 1905 (glass plate and print) (Item S-150.)
    - Front Façade before 1906 (glass plate) (Item S-151.)
    - Front Façade before 1906 (glass plate) (Item S-152.)
    - Front Façade before 1906 from Museum (glass plate) (Item S-153.)
    - Front Façade from frame of Library, 1905 (glass plate) (Item S-154.)
    - Front through Palms near Chemistry Building, 1940? (negative) (Item S-155.)
    - Front across Oval Lawn with "Faith" Statue, 1915? (glass plate) (Item S-156.)
    - Front across Oval Lawn, 1925 (negative and miscellaneous prints) (Item S-157.)
    - Front from Museum (print) (Item S-158.)
    - Front from Museum, 1903? (glass plate) (Item S-159.)
    - Front from destroyed Library Frame, 1907 (negative) (Item S-160.)
    - Front panorama from Museum, 1930? (negative) (Item S-161.)
    - School of Biology - Faculty - Labs - Hopkins Station (miscellaneous negatives and 1 print) (Item S-162.)
    - Front through Palms near Chemistry Building, 1940? (glass plate) (Item S-163.)
    - Front across Oval Lawn with "Faith" Statue, 1915? (glass plate) (Item S-164.)
    - Memorial Arch - Diagonal view (glass plate) (Item S-166.)
    - Front across Oval Lawn, 1925 (negative) (Item S-167.)
    - Front Façade (glass plate and print) (Item S-168.)
    - Front panorama from Museum, 1930? (4 negatives and 3 prints) (Item S-170.)
    - Church Front, 1920 (negative and print) (Item S-171.)
    - Church Front before 1906 (glass plate) (Item S-172.)
    - Church Front - Tree branches overhead, 1920 (negative and print) (Item S-173.)
    - Church Front (print) (Item S-174.)
    - Church Front through Arch of Memorial Court (negative and print) (Item S-175.)
    - Church Front through Arch of East Side of Quad (negative and print) (Item S-176.)
    - Church Front through Arch of Memorial Court (negative) (Item S-177.)
    - Church Front, 1916 (negative and print) (Item S-178.)
    - Church through Arches, 1920 (negative and print) (Item S-179.)
    - Church Front - Tree branches overhead, 1920 (negative) (Item S-180.)
    - Church Front - Tree branches overhead, 1920 (negative) (Item S-181.)
    - Church Side Detail, 1920 (negative) (Item S-182.)
    - Church Side through Arcade (negative) (Item S-183.)
    - Church from Inner Quad, 1910 (glass plate and print) (Item S-184.)
    - Church before 1906 (glass plate, negative and print) (Item S-185.)
    - Church before 1906 (glass plate, negative and print) (Item S-186.)
    - Church Front through Arch across the Quad before 1906 (glass plate and print) (Item S-187.)
    - Church Front (print) (Item S-188.)
    - Church Front through Arch across the Quad before 1906 (negative and print) (Item S-189.)
    - Church Rear, 1906 April 18 - Earthquake (negative) (Item S-191.)
    - Church Front, 1906 April 18 - Earthquake (negative and print) (Item S-192.)
    - Church Interior before 1906 (glass plate) (Item S-193.)
    - Church Interior (print) (Item S-194.)
    - Church Interior before 1906 (glass plate and print) (Item S-195.)
    - Church Interior after re-construction (negative and print) (Item S-196.)
    - Church Interior - Miscellaneous views before 1906 (glass plate and prints) (Item S-201.)
    - Church Interior before 1906 (glass plate) (Item S-202.)
    - Church - Miscellaneous Interior and Exterior Views after Earthquake (prints) (Item S-202-1 through 10.)
    - Church Interior toward Organ Loft after 1906 (negative) (Item S-203.)
    - Church Interior from Organ Loft after 1906 (negative) (Item S-204.)
    - Church Interior toward Chancel after 1906 Earthquake (negative and print) (Item S-205.)
    - Church Pulpit (glass plate and similar print) (Item S-206.)
    - Church Interior (glass plate and print) (Item S-207.)
    - Church Interior from Organ Loft before 1906 (glass plate) (Item S-208.)
    - Golf Club House, 1930 (negative) (Item S-209.)
    - Church Interior before 1906 - Church Wall Murals from Altar (negative and print) (Item S-210.)
    - Church Interior after re-construction (glass plate and print) (Item S-211.)
    - Church Organ (glass plate) (Item S-212.)
    - Church Organ (glass plate) (Item S-213.)
    - Church Organ (negative) (Item S-215.)
    - Church Organ Loft before 1906 (glass plate and print) (Item S-216.)
    - Church Mosaics on Side Wall (glass plate) (Item S-217.)
    - Church Mosaics on Side Wall showing Choir Loft (glass plate and print) (Item S-219.)
    - Church Interior from Organ Loft after Reconstruction (negative and print) (Item S-220.)
    - Church Interior from Organ Loft before 1906 (negative and print) (Item S-221.)
    - Church Mosaics on Side Wall (glass plate and print) (Item S-222.)
    - Church Mosaics on Side Wall (glass plate and print) (Item S-223.)
    - Church Mosaics on Side Wall (glass plate) (Item S-224.)
    - Church "Lord's Supper" in Mosaic (glass plate and print) (Item S-225.)
    - Church Adam and Eve (glass plate and print) (Item S-226.)
    - Church Adam and Eve (glass plate and print) (Item S-227.)
    - Church Rose Window before 1906 (glass plate and print) (Item S-228.)
    - Church Front straight-on (negative and print) (Item S-229.)
    - Frost Outdoor Theatre - Excavation, 1936 November 20 to 1937 February (miscellaneous negatives and print) (Item S-230.)
    - Memorial Theatre Construction, 1936 March 19 (negative and print) (Item S-231.)
    - Memorial Theatre - Seats and lights (negatives and prints) (Item S-232.)
    - Memorial Theatre - Seats and Lights (negative and print) (Item S-233.)
    - Dr. Harris J. Ryan - Portraits in Laboratory (negatives and print) (Item S-234.)
    - Ryan Laboratory (miscellaneous negatives) (Item S-235.)
    - Ryan Laboratory (negative and print) (Item S-236.)
    - Ryan laboratory (print) (Item S-237.)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory - Miscellaneous views (7 prints) (Item S-237-1.)
    - Chemistry Building before 1906 (negative and print) (Item S-238.)
    - Chemistry Building before 1906 (print) (Item S-238-1.)
    - Chemistry Building after earthquake (4 prints) (Item S-238-2 through 5.)
    - Chemistry Building, 1938. Also Plant Growing Research (miscellaneous negatives and print) (Item S-239.)
    - Chemistry Building (print) (Item S-239-1.)
    - Law School - Faculty portraits, 1936, and interior and exterior views of building (miscellaneous negatives and 1 print) (Item S-240.)
    - Dr. David Starr Jordan (glass plate and print) (Item S-241.)
    - Dr. Jordan, 50-60 years? (glass plate and print) (Item S-241-1.)
    - Dr. Jordan, about 70 years old (negative and print) (Item S-241-2.)
    - Dr. Jordan with dog (negative and print) (Item S-241-3.)
    - Dr. Jordan (negative) (Item S-241-4.)
    - Dr. Jordan (negative) (Item S-241-5.)
    - Dr. Jordan (negative and print) (Item S-241-6.)
    - Dr. Jordan profile (negative and print) (Item S-241-7.)
    - Dr. Jordan at desk (negative and print) (Item S-241-8.)
    - Dr. Jordan and Co-eds, 1908? (negative and print) (Item S-241-9.)
    - Dr. Jordan at bat and miscellaneous other baseball pictures (negative and print) (Item S-241-10.)
    - Dr. and Mrs. Jordan, seated in garden, 1929 (negative and print) (Item S-241-11.)
    - Dr. Jordan - Stanford Home (negative) (Item S-241-11A.)
    - Dr. Jordan and Dr. Ray Lyman Wilbur, 1916 May 20 (glass plate and print) (Item S-241-12.)
    - Dr. Jordan and Dr. Wilbur, 1916 June (glass plate and print) (Item S-241-13.)
    - Dr. Jordan in Quad, 1916 (negative and print) (Item S-241-14.)
    - Dr. and Mrs. Jordan and Dr. B. W. Evermann on SS Maui for Honolulu, 1924 July 23 (negative and print) (Item S-241-15.)
    - Dr. Jordan (negative and print) (Item S-241-16.)
    - Dr. Jordan (negative and print) (Item S-241-17.)
    - Dr. Jordan - Interior of home (negative) (Item S-241-18.)
    - Dr. Jordan - Interior of home (negatives) (Item S-241-18A & B.)
    - Dr. Jordan - Copy of part of Portrait painted by Spencer Macky, 1922 (negative and print) (Item S-241-19.)
    - Dr. Jordan, 1908 (negative and print) (Item S-241-20.)
    - Dr. and Mrs. Jordan (print) (Item S-241-21.)
    - Journalism Classes (miscellaneous negatives) (Item S-242.)
    - School of Social Sciences. Also Psychology (miscellaneous negatives) (Item S-243.)
    - Engineering School buildings (miscellaneous negatives) (Item S-244.)
    - Engineering School buildings from Church, 1925 (negative and print) (Item S-244-18.)
    - Engineering School buildings from Church, 1925 (negative and print) (Item S-244-19.)
    - Engineering School buildings (print) (Item S-244-20.)